FILING FOR LOVE
Is he still waiting
in the emergency room?
No, there's no need.
I'll call you back.
I'll just get off here.
It's still pretty far from here.
Just past the intersection...
In-a!
Excuse me. Nurse?
Doesn't he need surgery right away?
Why is there a delay?
Let me find out. Just a moment.
Don't we have any available OR yet?
They're full. The one that's left
is being prepped for a VIP.
- Why?
- Then
can't you organize
a transfer or a temporary OR?
Do something!
You can't just leave him here!
In-a.
You can help, Jae-yeol, can't you?
Call someone at Haemu Hospital.
Please, I beg of you. Help him out.
TIME IN SURGERY
TIME IN SURGERY, ANESTHETIC DURATION
CURRENT TIME
Out of all the trauma surgeons,
Dr. Yoon is the best.
Don't you worry.
I'll keep an eye on the patient, too.
- Thank you, director.
- Bye, then.
OPERATION ROOM
Mr. Noh, are you awake?
Mr. Noh.
EPISODE 8:
DESIRE & HOPE
HAEMU GENERAL HOSPITAL
I'm coming for you!
- Stop!
- No!
Catch me if you can!
Do you think this is
some kids' playground?
I'm a patient, okay?
I need some peace and quiet to rest!
Hey, we brought you
some expensive food, so eat it!
No, thanks. I lost my appetite.
You can eat it all.
You poor thing. You have no appetite?
Tell me if there's anything you want.
I'll make it for you.
By the way...
I haven't seen that lady recently.
The head of your department.
You're right.
When you were unconscious,
she came by all the time
and wouldn't stop looking at you
with those forlorn eyes.
I haven't seen her since you woke up.
Do you think you'd feel better
if she were to visit?
You woke up when she was with you.
Hey.
What's going on between you two?
She didn't seem like just a coworker.
There's more to it, isn't there?
She's not just your boss.
She's your sweet darling, isn't she?
Will you stay out of my business?
Is my little brother embarrassed?
Oh, you cutie pie.
What's wrong with you?
That smells amazing.
You treat me like
I'm your errand girl.
Who craves a toasted sandwich
at the crack of dawn?
It made you come to see me.
I came by because I was afraid.
Who sends over 20 texts
asking for a toasted sandwich?
What were you so afraid of
when I was unconscious
that made you look after me
around the clock for days?
My sisters told me all about it.
They said they were moved to tears.
I was afraid.
It was scary.
And also...
As your superior,
I should look out for you.
I was just checking in
to see if you were dead or alive.
Sure, I bet you were just looking out
for an employee.
But since you're looking out
for me anyway
could you get me discharged
and take me home?
- You're asking me to do that?
- Yes.
Handle that box with care.
There are quite a few breakables.
Why is there so much luggage
when you were stuck in a ward?
They deliver all sorts of things
to hospitals these days.
What am I even doing here?
Why should I get you discharged
and take you home, too?
I still have stitches in my stomach
and I have so much stuff
with no one else to help.
Isn't this the least you can do
for your staff?
Wait and see.
As soon as those stitches come out
I'll make you work extra hard
to make up for the time you wasted.
Sure.
That's the truth.
That area is very undervalued.
You think redevelopment is old news
but land always retains its value.
It does.
Do something!
You can't just leave him here!
Please, I beg of you. Help him out.
Don't you agree, Jae-yeol?
- I'm not sure.
- Goodness...
He never gets the timing right.
You seem to be against the idea
of turning that place upside-down.
A lot of people would lose
their homes and livelihoods.
They get compensated for that.
We don't kick them out penniless.
My brother is so softhearted.
He could never turn a blind eye
to people in need since he was young.
He always makes a sacrifice
or gives up what's his.
The Jeons are known to be ruthless.
You know what my father's like.
He's the most ruthless businessman
in the country.
I just don't get
who Jae-yeol takes after.
What I do know
is that he's not like our father.
He must be like his mom.
Sorry. I apologize instead.
He had too much to drink.
I contacted the PR Team. Get his car.
I'll bring the VP downstairs now.
Hello, A-jeong.
Why are you acting out of character?
You can't lash out like this
when a board meeting's coming up.
Will you let me off today?
Joo In-a...
What on earth is she to you?
She's someone I would die with.
How could you not keep an umbrella
in your car for emergencies?
I should get one for you
for next time.
If A-jeong's home,
why don't you ask her to bring one?
Why should we bother her?
It's a passing shower.
I'll wait until it stops raining.
Why did you and A-jeong break up?
I don't exactly know why.
She ghosted me out of the blue.
Didn't you ask her why?
You must've seen her at work.
I didn't ask.
I assumed there was a reason
she didn't tell me.
Why do you ask?
Would you have asked
if you were in my place?
If that had been me...
If I were A-jeong
I would have wanted you to ask.
Oddly enough, I have a habit
of hiding the truth
when it matters most.
While on the inside
I hope someone
would drag the truth out of me.
wouldn't give up on me.
I get selfish and contradictory.
Wouldn't it be easier
just to be honest?
Do you mean that?
So what?
- You want me to get married?
- Yes, I mean it.
Should we elope or something?
And get disowned and lose everything?
- I don't want that kind of life.
- In-a.
Either way
I was never naive enough
to think what we had
would last forever.
You can get married freely.
There's no need to feel guilty.
I really am
okay with it.
I think it's because
I don't know how to be happy.
Just when I think I'm happy,
I feel uneasy and anxious.
I ask myself,
"Do I even deserve this?"
I get afraid.
I hide and run away.
I'm just more used to being unhappy.
Close your eyes.
- What for?
- Come on.
I won't do anything weird.
Relax and close your eyes.
Okay.
What do you hear?
I hear the rain. What else?
Calm yourself and focus
on the sounds around you.
The sound of raindrops
hitting the windows.
And?
"And"?
- The car's engine.
- And?
A passing motorcycle.
What else?
Kids laughing
in the distance.
And?
The sound of your breath.
My heartbeat.
That's how you feel it.
If you look within yourself
just hard enough
with all your heart
happiness is right there.
It's always there
so whenever you want to find it
do what you did just now.
Welcome back!
- Glad you're okay.
- Thank you.
You had a tough time, Mr. Noh.
But you look
even better than before.
Did the hospital food
suit your taste?
He looks better
because he was away from work.
Don't be silly.
Mr. Noh always looked good.
The office is brighter
now that you're back.
Welcome back.
I missed you so very much, Mr. Noh.
Don't go overboard.
You don't have to worry
about Mr. Ahn.
Legal is taking an aggressive stance.
He'll pay a hefty price.
It looks like his family
cut ties with him, too.
He brought it upon himself.
You did well, Mr. Noh.
Thanks.
Your teammates must love you.
You didn't want to transfer
in the beginning, though.
- You wanted to transfer.
- Yes, more than anything.
Yes, that's true.
Good morning, Ms. Joo.
- Hello.
- Morning.
You're back, Mr. Noh.
Yes, I'm back, Ms. Joo.
Ms. Joo.
Do you have special plans for later?
You look nicer than usual.
I almost didn't recognize you.
Are you saying I looked dowdy before?
No, that's not what I meant.
You must be in a good mood
for some reason.
Could it be the return
of your favorite employee?
- I don't expect a lavish welcome...
- Mr. Noh.
You lost touch with how things are
while you were away.
I should help you return to reality.
I guess Ms. Joo still dislikes you.
I think the stabbing
didn't really change anything.
It's fine.
This is nothing.
I'm Noh Ki-jun,
the ace of the Audit Team.
Thanks.
Okay, let's do this.
I finished all the tasks you gave me.
AUDIT TEAM HEAD JOO IN-A
OK
"OK"?
This is too much.
My first day after a stabbing...
You worked hard today.
I'll treat you to a meal.
You will? When?
AUDIT TEAM HEAD JOO IN-A
Friday evening. Come to my place.
What's the matter?
- It's my back.
- Is your back sore?
Mr. Noh.
Hey, Doo-gi.
I'm sorry I couldn't visit you
in the hospital.
Don't be.
I won't visit you in the hospital
if you ever get stabbed.
We're even.
Fine, whatever.
Oh, right.
I have a work-related question.
- Yes?
- You handled Haemu Pharmaceutical.
Yes, I did.
Were you working
on anything in particular?
What are you talking about?
I handed over all the files.
Didn't you check the cloud server?
Yes, I did,
but I didn't find anything.
- Was the folder empty?
- Yes.
- I'll check and get back to you.
- Okay.
It's an important audit
on one of our subsidiaries.
Let me finish it.
Put all the info on our cloud server.
I'll take a look
and allocate someone else.
NOH KI-JUN'S PROJECT TRANSFER
NO FILES OR FOLDERS
NAMED NOH KI-JUN'S PROJECT TRANSFER
Hey, Jae-hong. Are you busy?
I need a favor.
A folder I uploaded
to our cloud server vanished.
RICE
20KG
Yes, this is perfect.
Can I help you?
Oh, yes.
What would you recommend
to give someone who is recovering?
Korean beef is the best.
What are you going to cook?
What dish looks difficult
but easy to cook
and looks complicated
but simple to prepare?
Just give me everything here.
- All of this?
- I need to practice.
Okay.
That folder was deleted
two days later.
It was accessed from Joo In-a's desk.
HAEMU PHARMACEUTICAL
CONFIRMATION NEEDED,
HAEMU PHARMA BUSINESS REPORT
BUSINESS REPORT
HAEMU PHARMACEUTICAL INC.,
CEO JEON JAE-YEOL
Put the garlic cloves sideways.
This is whole fresh garlic.
We'll cut them in half as well.
It won't taste as good
if the slices are too thin.
The more garlic
you use in this recipe
the more flavor
and health benefits there are.
Let's see...
Put the pot on the cooker
- and add two spoons of sesame oil.
- Add oil...
- Wait. Sesame oil.
- One spoonful of garlic.
Sesame oil. I don't have any oil.
CANOLA OIL, GROUND GARLIC,
PERILLA SEED OIL, SESAME OIL
All right.
It tastes so good. My gosh.
Mr. Noh?
Did you come in this early?
Or you didn't go home?
Mr. Noh, is something wrong?
On your first day here.
Why did you really transfer me
to Audit Team Three?
Are you still upset I put you
in charge of PM cases?
I don't at all think
PM cases are trivial.
You worked on enough cases to know
how personal matters
can affect business matters.
And they're harder to handle
because emotions are involved.
I believed that
with your confidence and intuition
that keep you from being swayed
you'd be able to handle them well,
and I was right.
Is that all?
Is there really
no other reason?
Jei Medical Foundation.
Haemu Pharma donates to them as part
of Corporate Social Responsibility.
There's no problem with that.
However...
They were extremely generous
even when Jei Medical Foundation was
unknown and had no results to show.
So...
DONATIONS
I kept digging
and followed lead after lead.
DONATIONS MADE IN 2021
JEI MEDICAL FOUNDATION:
400 MILLION WON
It was awfully complicated.
JEI MEDICAL FOUNDATION:
500 MILLION WON
But the actual owner
of this entity is
Vice President Jeon Jae-yeol.
This foundation
was founded by Mr. Jeon, right?
Now tell me.
Are they related?
This case and
why you sent me to Team Three.
Let's make a minor change
to your role, Mr. Noh.
NOH KI-JUN, AUDIT TEAM 1 TURNOVER
DELETE PERMANENTLY
DO YOU WISH TO PERMANENTLY DELETE
ALL FOLDERS AND FILES?
YES
FOLDER WAS PERMANENTLY DELETED
Yes, I halted the investigation.
But I'd concluded that VP Jeon
didn't profit from the foundation
nor were there issues
within Haemu Pharmaceutical.
But that's...
I don't think
that's for you to decide.
You should've reported this
and alerted the board of executives
so they could carry out
a special investigation.
Shouldn't the call be made then?
Things would've snowballed
unnecessarily.
- It would've become political...
- And he would've gotten hurt.
VP Jeon, I mean.
Did he ask you to help him out?
He doesn't know that I know.
You're meticulous with a clear
distinction between work and life.
Did you really sweep this
under the rug yourself
for fear that our VP would get hurt?
Even if I don't do anything,
this will come out.
So do whatever it takes
to be yourself
and correct this.
- Hi.
- Ms. Joo's here.
- You came in early, Mr. Noh.
- Good morning.
- Morning, Ms. Joo.
- Hello.
Nice and moist.
I feel refreshed.
You're home.
You're late.
Hey.
Did you drink?
Hello, Chairman.
This is Joo In-a speaking.
I have one additional report to make
at tomorrow's board meeting.
In that case,
the last item also passed.
Head of Audit,
would you like to speak?
I'd like to share an additional issue
I could not previously report
during the Audit Committee
here at the board meeting.
One moment, Ms. Joo.
There's an agenda
that wasn't presented beforehand.
Director Park Sang-hwan
has something he'd like to suggest.
- Please speak.
- Yes.
I ask for your understanding
in this sudden discussion.
The president is currently unable
to fully carry out
official duties
due to health-related issues.
Thus, the majority
of business decisions
are solely made
by Vice President Jeon Jae-yeol.
However, the president
is still standing strong.
Also, his condition does not change
the fact that he's our leader
and the group's anchor.
On that note, in order to promote
more effective decision-making
and stable management conditions
I suggest appointing
Managing Director Jeon Sang-yeol
as the co-vice president.
What's going on with Director Park?
Wasn't he with the vice president?
He must've betrayed him.
Silence, everyone.
Now, let us vote on the agenda
which Director Park has proposed.
Those who agree to appoint
Managing Director Jeon Sang-yeol
as the co-vice president
with Vice President Jeon Jae-yeol,
please raise your hand.
Hello, Director Park.
- I owe it all to you. Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
I should start lining up
on his side, too.
- Congratulations, Mr. Jeon.
- Ms. Joo.
The sudden agenda had me flustered,
so I forgot about you.
Did you say you had
another item to report on?
Would you like
to report it in writing?
- No, there's nothing, sir.
- All right.
- Mr. Managing Director.
- Now the vice president.
Goodness.
Please help me out.
- Why don't we go out and eat?
- Sure.
Congratulations.
I owe it to you.
I'll need your guidance.
- Goodness, you don't need that.
- I do.
THE RECENT BOARD MEETING WAS INSANE
THE DIRECTORS UNDER THE VP
HAVE LINED UP UNDER DIRECTOR JEON
No way. So do we need approval
from two vice presidents from now on?
Goodness. How will things work out
in the office?
Isn't it obvious?
We should side with S.
I heard this
from the executive assistants.
Director Park used to be
on Vice President Jeon's side
but suddenly betrayed him
during this meeting.
- My gosh.
- Office politics are scary.
Gosh, so this is how it turned out.
- What now?
- Whose side are you on?
- Me?
- Yes.
- I'm on your side.
- Cut it out.
What about you?
The report on the director... No.
MR. NOH KI-JUN
Your call cannot be connected.
You will be redirected to voicemail.
After the beep,
you will be charged...
JOO IN-A
SEARCH: JOO IN-A
BOO SE-YOUNG, HEAD OF HR
Hey, do you realize
what time it is right now?
Se-young.
Can you do me a favor?
You can't do this so suddenly.
I thought my appointment
to the US was put on hold.
Yes, for a moment
while you were unwell.
You got better, so you need to go.
I'm not completely well yet.
I'm getting treated as an outpatient.
There are hospitals in the US, too.
Don't worry.
And the company will cover
all medical costs.
Isn't that amazing?
Does Ms. Joo know
about this sudden appointment?
What do you mean?
- She asked me to do this.
- Sorry?
She called me early this morning
to arrange for you
to go abroad as soon as possible.
Instead, she asked me to give you
the special promotion now
and send you to the best branch
with the easiest workload.
I guess In-a
really adores you.
GIVING AWAY
1G OF GOLD BAR
Have all these been confirmed
during the previous audit?
Yes, there was also
a huge organizational change
so I reprinted the sheet.
Ms. Joo, may I speak with you?
I'm in the middle of a report.
We need to talk right now!
Where are your manners,
Mr. Noh Ki-jun?
Wait until Mr. Ahn is done.
What do you want to talk about?
You already know.
What's going on
with my appointment to the US?
It was already confirmed
that you were going.
It's a great opportunity for you
and if you're going anyway,
it's better to go soon.
In the California branch,
you'll get to experience
more business management
than conducting audits.
Don't give me those.
What's the real reason?
Is it
because of Jei Medical Foundation?
I'm not some kind of wuss
who can't understand that.
I honestly blamed myself
thinking if I had cornered you
too harshly.
"Sure, when someone
you barely knew back in school
suddenly shows up with a favor,
even that's difficult to turn down.
So she may want to cover up
her ex-boyfriend's mishap."
I thought I overreacted and regretted
getting carried away by my emotions.
You didn't overreact.
I can't promise you
that I will right the wrong.
Why not?
Are you afraid
Jeon Jae-yeol will get hurt?
Are you going back to him?
Just as the Little Prince
returned to the planet for his rose
are you also going back
to Jeon Jae-yeol?
- No, that's not the case.
- Then what?
How am I supposed to understand
this whole situation?
Do I
owe you an explanation?
You'll be busy getting ready to go,
so you're excused from your duties.
Good luck with the preparations.
INTERVIEW ROOM
Hey, man. You're acting recklessly
against Ms. Joo
just because
you're leaving for the US soon.
Right? I was in shock.
Anyway, what did you two talk about
in the interview room?
Wait, we're here to celebrate him.
Why has he been downing drinks
with that frown on his face?
Tell me about it.
It's a great occasion.
Wait, is it because
you don't want to buy us a drink?
Hey, no way.
Excellent.
I think you should come along
to the Jeju business trip, Ms. Joo.
Me?
What's there
for the Audit Team to do?
You were with CPK and JV
while you worked abroad.
You'll help break the ice
as an experienced partner.
In that case, Ms. Joo must go.
Gosh, I'm jealous.
Jeju must be nice around this time.
It's my birthday.
So why don't I grab a drink?
JEON JAE-YEOL
DESTINATION: JEJU
Hi. Let's have a drink.
It's been a while.
You heard me at the meeting, right?
Get me ready
for the business trip next week.
Why Ms. Joo In-a?
There are more than enough reasons
for Ms. Joo In-a to accompany me.
She's an experienced partner
who knows the other party.
Not that, but the real reason.
What do you think you're doing?
No, what do you think you're doing?
Not only do you get
into a drunken fight
but you're sending an employee
overseas because of your feelings.
Do you know
what people are saying about you?
That the managing director
will become the president
and you'll be kicked out.
"Will he leave without causing a mess
or lose everything miserably?"
They're saying
those two are the only options.
In times like these
why do you keep making mistakes
because of uncontained emotions?
I'm used to hearing
people talk like that.
And I regret
letting those have an effect
on acting true to my emotions.
So what now?
What can you do
by being true to your emotions?
Are you going to die with Joo In-a?
You said she was a woman
you could die with.
Ms. Park A-jeong, you seem to be
the one who's emotional, not me.
So?
Can you even give up everything
for that woman?
If I must.
What are these?
Why did I get this?
I never even use it.
From now on, I swear
to live as a minimalist.
Hey, just leave those.
I'm sure there are dishes in the US.
You can use them.
Anyway, come to think of it,
I'm glad you moved in here.
It would've been too much work
to rent out the place while I'm gone.
Hey, are you listening?
Ki-jun.
Do you know that
the vice president and Joo In-a
are going to Jeju next week?
I do. I saw the schedule.
They've traveled there together.
It must be such a dear memory.
He even kept the old plane ticket.
Sounds humble.
I didn't know even rich people
like him go to Jeju as a couple.
Hey, I said you can use that cup.
Did you pack all these?
Just leave these dishes
back in the cupboard.
Are you okay?
I'll get it. That must be our food.
Ki-jun.
I'll step out for a moment.
We're out of drinking water.
- Okay. Sure.
- Excuse me.
What? Why? Did I do anything wrong?
I just explained everything.
She's renting out a room from me.
Stop pinching me, will you?
Hey, what is wrong with you?
You kept a woman
by your side at the hospital
but actually live with another?
Who do you think you are?
I'm a nobody. Okay?
But you know what?
That woman isn't into me.
What kind of nonsense is this?
Hey. How could she do that
if she wasn't into you?
I don't know, but she said
she likes another man.
So you forget about her, too.
You foolish idiot!
You can't just take her words
and take it as is.
Pay attention to her demeanor,
actions, and look in her eyes!
Think of the way she looked at you
while you were at the hospital.
Good grief. You're so slow.
Oddly enough, I have a habit
of hiding the truth
when it matters most.
- Hey.
- Where are they staying in Jeju?
- What?
- Where's Joo In-a staying in Jeju?
Why? Are you going to go after her?
I'm asking you! Where is she?
Jeon Jae-yeol, Noh Ki-jun.
You're both insane.
The terms don't look so bad
though you'll need to verify.
I'd prefer the investment
to be bigger.
But a higher risk
will come with that.
CPK is just a money-lending business.
There's no soul.
It's nice to be here with you.
Jeju, I mean.
It was our first and last trip.
We managed to take a leave
at the same time and come here
but only worked the whole time
just like we're doing now.
The biggest concern now
is the formation of the board.
In-a.
Mr. Vice President, it seems like
you're having a hard time focusing.
I'll look over this separately
and report back to you.
Wait, In-a.
Can we sit here...
like the old days for a moment?
That's not going to happen.
We can't go back
to how things used to be.
Then why did you return to Korea?
To honor what I said.
I promised to take your side.
So this is the last I can do
to honor my words.
That's more than enough.
I don't care how you feel
and why you're doing it.
Please just stay by my side.
That's all I need.
I'm done doing that, too.
I got caught up with that promise
and made a mistake I shouldn't have.
And I hurt someone.
I shouldn't have done that to him.
Are you talking about Mr. Noh Ki-jun?
What I'm trying to say is
I'm never going back to you,
Jae-yeol.
It must be far too late
to go to you.
Joo In-a!
Noh Ki-jun.
Why did you check out already?
I had to go all the way to the hotel.
HAEMU STRATEGIC PLANNING, MARKETING,
DIGITAL MARKETING, AUDIT TEAM 1, 2, 3
...IS INVOLVED IN AN INAPPROPRIATE
WORKPLACE RELATIONSHIP
MS. JOO IN-A...
SEND, HIDE SENDER
SEND
FILING FOR LOVE
I'm kind of worried
that I won't be able to hide
how much I like you at work.
Clear your schedule this weekend.
I booked a pool villa in Sokcho.
Mr. Noh, you should go
to Mr. Min's club
- this weekend.
- What?
You said you get passionate
when you start dating.
But all you did was
make me work passionately.
Mr. Noh, do you want to stay
for ramyeon?
You must be enjoying yourself
caught between two men.
I'm getting a divorce.
I regret everything, In-a.
What's going on?
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim